(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
START the SCREEN
ファンサ
作詞・作曲:HoneyWorks
Fans
Lyrics/Music: HoneyWorks
好きになって　もっと
Please love me more,
私を見て　もっと
Look at me more,
恩返しは　愛のこもった投げキッスで
I'll repay you with an air kiss full of love.
気のせいじゃない　目は合ってるよ
It's not your imagination, our eyes met.
ハート作って　恋しちゃってください
Make a heart and fall in love with me.
やれること　なんでもします
I'll do anything I can.
NGなしで　体当たり挑戦
No NGs, I'll give it my all.
エゴサで見つけたアンチのコメ
Anti comments I found while ego-searching.
ふざけんな　誰より分かってるし
Stop it! I know myself better than anyone.
でも大丈夫　ここに立てばみんながいる
But it's okay, because you're all here when I stand here.
行くよ！
Here we go!
好きになって　もっと
Please love me more,
私を見て　もっと
Look at me more,
恩返しは　愛のこもった投げキッスで
I'll repay you with an air kiss full of love.
虜にする　もっと
I'll captivate you more,
夢を見せる　もっと
I'll show you more dreams,
楽しんでって！愛のこもったスペシャルナイト
Please enjoy! A special night full of love.
ファンサしちゃうぞ
I'm giving you some fan service!
お手紙も　書いてください
Please write me letters too.
何度も読んで　宝物にします
I'll read them over and over and treasure them.
スキャンダル　まだ早いけど
A scandal... it's still too early, but...
裏切りません　宣言しときます
I won't betray you, I'll declare it now.
嫉妬嫌がらせには負けない
I won't lose to jealousy or harassment.
ふざけんな　実力で勝ってやる
Stop it! I'll win with my talent.
だからやめない　負けず嫌い私はいる
So I won't quit, my competitive self is here.
行くよ！
Here we go!
拳上げて　もっと
Raise your fists more,
汗をかいて　もっと
Work up a sweat more,
恩返しは　愛のこもったまつりビームで
I'll repay you with a Matsuri Beam full of love.
大歓声　もっと
A loud cheer, more,
まだまだね　もっと
Not yet, more,
受け止めてね　愛のこもったわがままソング
Please accept it, my selfish song full of love.
ファンサしちゃうぞ
I'm giving you some fan service!
終わりが近づく　寂しいね
The end is near, it's lonely, isn't it?
楽しいのに　泣きそうだよ
Even though it's fun, I feel like crying.
次も次もまた会えるよね
We'll see each other again and again.
約束！
I promise!
まつりす！誕生日、今年も祝ってくれてありがとう！
Matsurisu! Thank you for celebrating my birthday again this year!
来年も、再来年も、絶対、絶対祝ってくれよな！
You have to celebrate it next year and the year after too, definitely!
優しさに溢れている言葉も
Both words full of kindness
心ない誰かの言葉さえも
and even thoughtless words from someone.
必要なんだ　必要なんだ
They're all necessary, they're all necessary.
強くなろう
I'll become stronger.
好きに叫べ
Shout as much as you like.
もっと楽しんじゃえ
Have even more fun.
もっと忘れないで
Don't ever forget.
特別な日になりますように
I hope it becomes a special day.
共に歌おう　ずっと
Let's sing together, forever.
共に歩もう　ずっと
Let's walk together, forever.
合言葉は
Our secret password is
とびっきりのL-O-V-E
a very special L-O-V-E.
好きになって　もっと
Fall in love with me more.
まつりを見て　もっと
Look at Matsuri more.
恩返しは　愛のこもった投げキッスで
I'll pay you back with a loving blown kiss.
虜にする　もっと
I'll captivate you more.
夢を見せる　もっと
I'll show you more dreams.
楽しんでって　愛のこもったスペシャルナイト
Enjoy this loving special night.
ファンサしちゃうぞ
I'm going to give you some fan service!
はい、ということで早速聴いていただきました。ファンサでした。ありがとうございましたー！
Alright, so the first song was Fansa. Thank you so much!
はぁ、ちょっと一曲目から歌って踊って、息が上がっておりますけども。
Phew, singing and dancing from the very first song has me out of breath.
ということで改めまして、まつりすのみんな、見てるかー！？
So once again, all you Matsurisu out there, are you watching!?
今日はまつりちゃんの誕生日だー！イェーイ！祝いに来てくれてありがとうございます。
Today is Matsuri-chan's birthday! Yay! Thank you for coming to celebrate with me.
なんと、デビューしてから4回目のお誕生日を迎えたらしいですよ。
Believe it or not, this is my 4th birthday since my debut.
4回だよ！凄くない？凄いでございますね。
Four times! Isn't that amazing? It really is.
いやそんな中でね、1回目の誕生日は、あの、YouTubeの収益化がまだ通ってなくて、ツイキャスでやってたりとか。
Looking back, for my 1st birthday, YouTube monetization hadn't gone through yet, so I did it on TwitCasting.
2回目は、3Dあったっけ？っていうレベルなんですよ。
For the 2nd one, I'm like, "Did I even have 3D back then?"
なのでね、こうやって4回もみんなと誕生日を過ごすことができて、
So being able to spend four birthdays with everyone like this...
まあ初めての方も、2回目の方とかもいるかもしれないんですけども、本当に嬉しいなと思っております。
whether you're here for the first time or the second, I'm truly happy.
そして今回はね、ちょっと特別なものが色々あるので、見ていただきたい。
And this time, there are various special things I'd like you to see.
まずは、ちょっと背景にも映ってるんですけど、こちら、ドドン！
First of all, they're already in the background, but here they are, ta-da!
見える？これさ、これこれ！
Can you see them? These! These ones!
このスピーカーでございますよ。
These speakers.
はい、これね、まつりの髪飾りのスナギモっていうね、にゃんこがいるんですけど、そのにゃんこのスピーカー。
Yes, these are speakers shaped like Sunagimo, the kitty from my hair ornament.
そしてひまわり。まつりといえばひまわりみたいなとこありますからね。
And sunflowers. Sunflowers are kind of a Matsuri thing, after all.
ひまわりのスピーカーを作っていただきました。ありがとう、運営さーん！
They made these sunflower speakers for me. Thank you, staff!
ありがとうございます。超可愛いでしょ。
Thank you so much. They're super cute, right?
そしてそしてね、まだあります。もう見えてると思うんですけども、こちら、ジャン！
And also, there's more. I think you can already see it, but here, ta-da!
マイク！まつりのオリジナルのマイクでございます。
A microphone! This is Matsuri's original microphone.
超可愛くない？見える？
Isn't it super cute? Can you see?
リボン付いてて。ほら、ここ、後ろにもスナギモ付いてるんですよ。
It has a ribbon. And look, there's Sunagimo on the back too.
そう、で、バーチャルならではの、なんか、なんていうの？ホログラムっていうんですか？
Right, and it has these, what do you call them? Like holograms?
が、モモンモモンって周りに付いているわけでございますよ。
Floating around it, which is something only possible in virtual spaces.
これもね、もういつから？半年前くらいから全部ね、あの、運営さんと相談しながらね、
For this too, since when? About half a year ago, I was consulting with the staff about everything...
「どうしてもやりたいのでお願いします」って言って進めてきたのでね。
saying "I really want to do this, please," and we've been moving forward with it.
今日お披露目できて良かったなと思います。
I'm so glad I could unveil it today.
ということで、えー、もう次の曲に行きたいと思うんですけども。
So, well, I'd like to move on to the next song now.
まぁまつりはね、あの、好きな曲を今日、好きな人のために、とまつりすのために歌おうと思ってきたので。
Well, I came here today wanting to sing songs I love for the people I love, and for the Matsurisu.
まぁその中でも、まぁカバーになってしまうのですが、
Among those, although it's a cover...
あの、あれですね、まつりが一番好きなHoneyWorksさんの曲をここから2曲続けて歌わせていただきたいと思います。
well, I'd like to sing two songs in a row from HoneyWorks, who I love the most.
緊張する。
I'm nervous.
それでは聴いてください。「ナンバーワン」。
Please listen. "Number One."
No.1
作詞：shito, Gom 作曲：shito
Lyrics: shito, Gom / Composition: shito
ごめん、憧れてた 追いかけてた
Sorry, I was longing for it, chasing after it.
いつまでもそうでいたかった
I wanted to stay that way forever.
完璧なあなた嫌いになった
I grew to hate your perfect self.
同じように愛もらって育ったのに
Even though I was raised with the same love,
いつからか差が開いてた
at some point, a gap opened up.
八つ当たりだってしたかったね
I wanted to take it out on you, didn't I?
Maybe 神様は試練与えた 強く慣れよと
Maybe God gave me a trial, telling me to become stronger.
うざい平等なんて嘘つき 分かってるけど
I know "annoying equality" is a lie, but...
可愛いとか持てたいとか 諦めないの女の子だし
Being cute, wanting to be popular... I won't give up, I'm a girl after all.
可愛く 猫被り ナンバーワンだよ
Acting cute and innocent, I'm number one.
愛してね 生き方は 無限にある
Love me, okay? There are infinite ways to live.
お父さんの大袈裟な言葉
My dad's exaggerated words...
いじらしく 猫被り 私らしく行く
Adorably innocent, I'll go my own way.
暇じゃない人生生きよ
Let's live a life that's not boring.
だって理想言えばキリがなくて
Because if I talk about ideals, there's no end to it.
無いもの全部欲しがって
Wanting everything I don't have,
鏡を見たって溜息 はぁ...
I look in the mirror and sigh, "ha..."
あなただって悩んでいた 知らなかった
I didn't know you were worrying too.
みんなと同じだったとした
Assuming you were just like everyone else,
ピンと張った糸 緩んでいく
the taut string begins to loosen.
Maybe 神様は楽しんでる 予測できない人を
Maybe God is enjoying people who are unpredictable.
私はそれ以上に 楽しんでやるぜ
I'm going to enjoy it even more than that!
勉強とかお仕事とか 諦めないの女の子だし
Studying, working... I won't give up, I'm a girl after all.
元気よく 挨拶よく たまには不意に付いてきて
Energetic, good with greetings, sometimes follow me unexpectedly.
愛した分 愛されるの お母さんがくれたアドバイス
You'll be loved as much as you love, that's the advice my mom gave me.
張り切ってミスしても 私らしく行く
Even if I'm eager and make a mistake, I'll go my own way.
胸張って生きる
Live with your head held high.
さらけ出せば 心が温かてれたんだ
If I lay it all bare, my heart would be warmed.
好きに言ってろ 痛くない
Say what you want, it doesn't hurt.
神様は夢与えた 変われるために
God gave me a dream so that I could change.
サンキュ 乗ってやるよ 最後まで付き合ってもらうよ
Thank you, I'll take you up on that, stay with me until the end.
雨は止んで傘を閉じた 今まで見えてなかった景色
The rain stopped and I closed my umbrella, seeing views I couldn't see before.
透明が反射して世界を照らした
Transparency reflected and illuminated the world.
胸躍る 可愛いとか持てたいとか 諦めないの女の子だし
Exciting! Being cute, wanting to be popular... I won't give up, I'm a girl after all.
可愛く 猫被り ナンバーワンでしょ
Acting cute and innocent, I'm number one, right?
愛してね 生き方は無限にある
Love me, okay? There are infinite ways to live.
お父さんの大袈裟な言葉
My dad's exaggerated words...
いじらしく 猫被り まつりらしく行く
Adorably innocent, I'll go Matsuri's way.
暇じゃない人生生きよ
Let's live a life that's not boring.
可愛くね　とびきりの愛よ届け！
Be cute, send out my ultimate love!
よろしければ名前だけでも覚えてってください
If you'd like, please at least remember my name
レッスン開始　意気込んだけれど
Lessons started, I was so pumped up but...
歌って踊ってヘトヘト
Singing and dancing, I'm exhausted
比較されることもあるけど
I get compared to others sometimes but...
私は私でありたい
I want to be myself
本気出さなきゃ響かないんだ
If I don't give it my all, it won't resonate
ファンの心を掴みたいんだ
I want to grab the hearts of my fans
だからスタート全開飛ばしますよ
So I'm going full speed from the start!
可愛くね　とびきりの愛よ届け！
Be cute, send out my ultimate love!
よろしければ名前だけでも覚えてってください
If you'd like, please at least remember my name
あざとくね　とびきりのスマイルで
Be calculatedly cute, with an ultimate smile
よろしければ推しにしちゃってくれませんか？なんてね
If you'd like, won't you make me your "oshi"? Just kidding!
ちょっぴりマジなの　期待していいですか？
I'm a little serious, can I get my hopes up?
人生変えるそんな一日
A day that changes my life
憧れ夢見たステージ
The stage I've longed for and dreamed of
おしゃれ流行り追いつけなくて
I can't keep up with fashion or trends
言い訳弱音も出ちゃうよ
I end up making excuses and whining
向いてないかな？
Am I not cut out for this?
愛想悪いしこんなアイドル
I'm not very sociable, for an idol like this
他にいないし
There's no one else like me
でもね絶対絶対見返すんだ
But you know, I'll definitely, definitely show them!
愛してね　日本一夢見てる
Love me, I'm dreaming of being number one in Japan
よろしければ愛の手ひとつ入れてやってください
If you'd like, please give me a hand with your love
手を上げて　視線独り占めして
Raise your hands, monopolize my gaze
よろしければ愛を恵んでくれませんか？なんてね
If you'd like, won't you bestow your love upon me? Just kidding!
絶対後悔させませんよ　マジでね
I definitely won't let you regret it, for real
今もステージは胸がギュッと熱くなる
Even now, the stage makes my heart tighten with heat
揺れる景色焼き付けて
Burning the swaying scenery into my mind
歌う声に愛を込める
I put my love into my singing voice
ギター！
Guitar!
響く歓声　気持ち高鳴る
The echoing cheers make my heart race
これは証明　「まつり」ここだよ
This is proof, "Matsuri" is right here
行くよ！絶対絶対声出してね
Here I go! Definitely, definitely let me hear your voice!
可愛くね　とびきりの愛よ届け！
Be cute, send out my ultimate love!
よろしければ名前だけでも覚えてってください
If you'd like, please at least remember my name
あざとくね　とびきりのスマイルで
Be calculatedly cute, with an ultimate smile
よろしければ推しにしちゃってくれませんか？なんてね
If you'd like, won't you make me your "oshi"? Just kidding!
ちょっぴりマジなの　期待していいですか？
I'm a little serious, can I get my hopes up?
はい、ということでありがとうございましたー！
Alright, so, thank you very much!
えーちょっとね、あの連続で歌ったんで、ちょっと疲れてしまったんでMCをね、挟みたいと思いますよ。
Um, I sang several songs in a row, so I'm a bit tired, so I'd like to have an MC break.
いやね、可愛いステージに可愛いマイクに、本当にさっきもね、あの紹介したんですけど、嬉しいね。
I mean, this cute stage and cute mic, I really did introduce them earlier, but it makes me happy.
でも、実はまだまだね、見せてないものがあるんですよ。
But, actually, there are still things I haven't shown you yet.
なのでちょっと見せちゃおうかな？
So maybe I'll show you a bit?
それでは行きますよ。
Alright, here we go.
チェンジ！
Change!
はい！お！おお！
Hi! Oh! Ohhh!
ということで、なんと。
And so, check this out.
イヤホンマイクって言うんですか？こう耳に付ける感じのね。
Is it called an earphone mic? The kind you clip on your ear.
可愛らしいのがあるじゃないですか。可愛いね。可愛いね。
Isn't it just adorable? So cute. So cute.
ということで、この後の曲は...
So, for the next song...
ちょっとマイク、手持ちマイクじゃなくて、こちらのマイクを使っていきたいと思います！
Instead of a handheld mic, I'll be using this one!
いや、今年はね、結構いろんなことがありまして。
Man, so much has happened this year.
3周年でね、あの、1期生とライブをやったりとかもしたんですけど。
Like for my 3rd anniversary, I did a live concert with the 1st gen members.
あれからもう1ヶ月半経ってるらしいですよ。
Apparently, it's already been a month and a half since then.
もうね、早いね、時の流れって。もう誕生日だなって思って。
Time really flies, doesn't it? It's already my birthday.
すぐね、4周年が来てしまうんじゃないかっていう感じなんですけども。
I feel like my 4th anniversary will be here in the blink of an eye.
まあ、今年そして来年は、新しいことに挑戦しつつも...
Well, for this year and the next, while challenging myself with new things...
まあ安定期というか、あの、楽しく、ゆるく、長く続けられるように...
I also want to enter a stable phase. To keep going for a long time at a fun, relaxed pace...
出来たらいいなと思っておりますのでね、あの、よろしくお願いします。
I hope I can achieve that. So, please keep supporting me.
来年の誕生日もぜひね、祝ってくださいよ。
Please make sure to celebrate my birthday next year too!
ということで、続いての曲なんですけども。
So, moving on to the next song.
次はソロじゃなくて...
This time, it's not a solo...
なんか、誰かが来る気がするんですよね。
I have a feeling someone is going to show up.
いや、来ないかな？来ないかな？
Wait, maybe not? Maybe they won't come?
来るかな？
Will they?
おー！
Whoa!
1期生が来てくれたぞー！
The 1st generation is here!
1期生が来たぞ！
The 1st gen is in the house!
来ちゃったよー！
We're here!
来たー！
They're here!
あれ？薄っぺらいのがいますけど。薄っぺらいのがいらっしゃいますが。
Wait, someone's looking a bit flat. There's a very thin person here.
気のせいかな？気のせいかな？ちょっと横向いてもらってもいいですか？
Is it just me? Could you turn to the side for a second?
薄い！薄っ！ペラちゃまだ、ペラちゃまが。
Thin! So thin! It's Pera-chama! Pera-chama is here.
ペラちゃま。ペラちゃま可愛い。
Pera-chama. Pera-chama is so cute.
来てくれましたね。ペラちゃま可愛い。
She actually came. Pera-chama is so cute.
ということで、今回はね、1期生の皆が集まってくれたのでね。
So, since everyone from the 1st gen has gathered here today...
まつりを祝ってほしいなと思うところでございますのですけども。
I'd like you all to celebrate Matsuri.
ちょっと誕生日だしプレゼントとして、まつりのお願い、1個ずつ聞いてもらいたいんだけど。
Since it's my birthday, as a present, I want to ask one favor from each of you.
いいですか？いいですか？
Is that okay? Is that okay?
なんだろう？なんだろう？
What is it? What could it be?
じゃあ、ちょっと、あの、カメラさんがいると思うので、こちらに。
Well, since we have the cameraman over there...
あの、1人ずつ、アキロゼからちょっと近づいてもらって。
I'd like you to approach the camera one by one, starting with AkiRose.
あの、まつりに、「まつりちゃん好きだよ」っていう一言を...
I want you to say "I love you, Matsuri-chan" to me...
ちょっとこれ、永久保存版にしたいので。
Because I want to keep this recorded for all eternity.
ぜひちょっと、あの、BGMとかも全部ない、この状況で、お願いします。
So please, in this quiet moment with no BGM, go ahead.
それでは、ちょっとアキロゼの告白まで、3、2、1、キュー！
And now, for AkiRose's confession... 3, 2, 1, cue!
まつりちゃん、大好きだよ。
Matsuri-chan, I love you.
あいだ、あいだ！恥ずかしい！
Stop it, stop it! That's so embarrassing!
あらあら、あらあら。
My, my. My, my.
じゃあ続いては、白上さん。
Okay, next up, Shirakami-san.
白上さんは何と、まつりの嫁宣言をちょっと、してもらおうかな。
For Shirakami-san, I'd like her to declare herself as Matsuri's wife.
私、白上フブキは、まつりちゃんの嫁ですって、お願いしていいですか？
Can you please say, "I, Shirakami Fubuki, am Matsuri-chan's wife"?
嫁でいいんですか？ハードル上がってるね。
You want me to be your wife? The stakes are getting higher.
それでは、白上さんの嫁宣言まで、3、2、1、キュー！
And now, for Shirakami-san's wife declaration... 3, 2, 1, cue!
えー、私、白上フブキは、えー、本日より...
Um, I, Shirakami Fubuki, from this day forward...
まあ、デビューしてからかとは思いますけども、改めて...
Well, I guess it's been the case since my debut, but once again...
まつりちゃんの嫁であるということを、ここに宣言させていただきます。
I hereby declare that I am Matsuri-chan's wife.
いぇーい！
Yay!
おめでとうございます。
Congratulations.
なに嫁がいいんだよ。
Why am I so happy about having a wife?
なに嫁がいるんだよ。嬉しい。
I can't believe I have a wife now. I'm so happy.
いいプレゼントだ。それでは、最後は、メルメル。
What a great present. And finally, Mel-mel.
メルメルには何をさせる気？
What are you planning to make Mel-mel do?
メルメルは、いつも、メルがカプカプする方だけど...
Mel-mel, you're usually the one doing the biting, but...
今日はまつりちゃんにカプカプされたいなって、照れ顔で言ってもらおうかな。
Today, I want you to say "I want to be bitten by Matsuri-chan" with a bashful face.
センシティブだなあ。色気ある感じでお願いしますよ。
That's quite spicy. Please do it with some sex appeal.
それでは、メルメルのそんなセリフまで、3、2、1、キュー！
Now, for Mel-mel's special line... 3, 2, 1, cue!
まつりちゃん、いつもメルがカプカプする側だけど...
Matsuri-chan, I'm usually the one who does the biting...
今日はまつりちゃんに、カプカプ、されたいな。
But today, I want to be... bitten by Matsuri-chan.
してあげる！
I'll do it for you!
やめなさい、やめなさい。満足満足。
Stop it, stop it. I'm satisfied, so satisfied.
全ての欲求を満たしたぜ。
All my desires have been fulfilled.
誕生日おめでとう！
Happy Birthday!
ありがとうございます。本当に。
Thank you so much. Truly.
口角が上がりすぎて、ちょっとほっぺ痛いんですけども。
My smile is so wide that my cheeks actually hurt.
この5人が集まったということは...
Since the five of us are gathered here...
ほう...
Ho...
やっぱりあの曲を歌わないと始まらないですよね！
It wouldn't be right if we didn't sing *that* song!
なんだなんだ？
What is it?
え、何なんだ？
Wait, what is it?
あれだね、あれ！
It's that one, right?
あれしかないよね！わかるわかる！
It has to be that one! I get it!
大丈夫？準備いい？
Are you okay? Ready?
もちろん！もちろん！
Of course! Of course!
オッケー！
Okay!
それじゃあいくよ！ミュージックスタート！
Alright, here we go! Music start!
Plasmagic Seasons!
作詞：森本練　作曲・編曲：森本練・竹市佳伸
Lyrics: Ren Morimoto / Composition & Arrangement: Ren Morimoto, Yoshinobu Takeichi
輝く夜空 四季巡って
Across the shining night sky, the four seasons pass
春風君を乗せて 夏色が迎えるよ
Carrying you on the spring breeze, the colors of summer welcome you
煌めく秋が背中を押したら
As the sparkling autumn gives you a push
真っ白 吹雪き煌めく めぐりめぐはーと
Pure white, a blizzard sparkles, hearts keep circling
何にもわからない一歩進んで
Taking a step forward without knowing anything
やっとここまで辿り着けたね
We've finally made it this far
待ちわびてる ずっと
I've been waiting for a long time
素敵なステージ 一番に
This wonderful stage, above all else
絶対見せてあげるよ (Oh!)
I'll definitely show it to you (Oh!)
Fly Fly Fly into your future
無邪気に回る季節が世界を
The innocently turning seasons
駆け巡って 夢のような君へと
Traverse the world, heading towards you who are like a dream
Bright Bright Light of your future
僕らがいた証をさあ 手を繋げよう
Let's hold hands to show the proof that we were here
スポットライトはついたばかり
The spotlight has only just been turned on
赤らむ心 イルミネーション
Blushing hearts, like illuminations
心は色とりどり 弾け舞うフェスティバル
Our hearts are multicolored, a festival bursting into dance
幸せいっぱい注ごう ロゼグラス
Let's pour plenty of happiness into our rose glasses
鳴らして キラッと染めるよ 真っさらな気持ち
Make them ring out, I'll dye my brand new feelings with a sparkle
12時の鐘なんて忘れちゃって
Forget about things like the clock striking midnight
ずっと解けない魔法をかけよう
Let's cast a spell that will never be broken
ときめかして そっと
Making my heart throb, gently
胸躍る時間を 送るから
Because I'll give you a heart-pounding time
絶対ついておいでよ (Oh!)
You definitely have to follow me (Oh!)
Pop Pop Pop of your future
今を駆ける五つ星 世界を
Five stars dashing through the present
巻き込んで 賑やかに遊ぼう
Let's involve the world and play lively
Flash Flash Flash of your future
目も眩むシチュエーション まだ 踊り足りないでしょ
A dazzling situation. You haven't danced enough yet, have you?
カーテンコールはずっとずっと先まで
The curtain call is still a long, long way off
楽しむ気持ち さえ持ってきたら
If you just bring a heart that's ready to have fun
きっと誰もが主役になれるよ
I'm sure anyone can become the protagonist
あの日も今日も 笑顔をさらけ出して
Both back then and today, show your smile
もっとステップ もっとジャンプ ジャンプ 重なるよ この世界を
Step more, jump more, jump. They overlap with this world.
一緒に遊び尽くそう (Oh!)
Let's play to our hearts' content together (Oh!)
Clap Clap Clap into your future
このメロディが終わっても 決して 今日だけの 思い出にはしないよ
Even if this melody ends, I will never let this be a memory of only today
Fly Fly Fly into your future
無邪気に回る季節が世界を 駆け巡って 夢のような君へと
The innocently turning seasons traverse the world, heading towards you who are like a dream
Bright Bright Light of your future
僕らがいた証をさあ 手を繋げよう
Let's hold hands to show the proof that we were here
スポットライトは終わらない
The spotlight will never end
デイリーダイアリー！
Daily Diary!
青春実況中 (いけーいけー)
Youth live broadcasting (Go, go!)
挑戦配信中 (ためしてみて)
Challenge streaming (Give it a try!)
青春実況中 (いっぱい)
Youth live broadcasting (Plenty!)
挑戦配信中 (あそぼおー)
Challenge streaming (Let's play!)
ほらね 楽しいは 発見
See, fun is a discovery
もっと新しい 好きが見つかったよ
I found a brand new 'like'
なになにー？超気になるー！
What is it? I'm so curious!
近所にできた カフェのケーキ
A cake from the cafe that opened nearby
なんかすごく美味しかったんだよ
It was somehow incredibly delicious
実食レポ 待ってまーす！
Waiting for the taste-test report!
知らなかったゲームや新作
Games and new titles I didn't know
聴いたことない歌 新曲
Songs and new tracks I've never heard
ちょっと気になったら手を伸ばしちゃう
If I'm even a bit interested, I'll reach out
ほら 一緒に遊ぼう (配信！)
Look, let's play together (Streaming!)
10連ガチャ引いてみよう (ほしい！)
Let's try pulling a 10-roll gacha (I want it!)
あのゲームやってみよう (よいしょー！)
Let's try playing that game (Heave-ho!)
あの曲歌ってみよう (おっとー！)
Let's try singing that song (Whoops!)
全部が お楽しみなの
Everything is part of the fun
窓の向こうの笑顔に手を振っちゃう
Waving my hand to the smiles beyond the window
あの日々中中 発見
In those daily discoveries
まぶたの裏に 秘めるポテンシャル
The potential hidden behind my eyelids
決め手のない漫画や名作
Manga without a clincher, or masterpieces
思いついた新ネタ 爆笑
A new gag I thought of, roaring laughter
新しい天気予報もきっと
The new weather forecast will surely
面白いことになるんだよ (配信！)
Turn into something interesting (Streaming!)
聞いて聞いて 今日の朝 (なになに？)
Listen, listen, earlier this morning (What is it?)
目覚まし鳴らなくって (それで？)
The alarm didn't go off (And then?)
寝過ごしちゃったのは (うっそー！)
The fact that I overslept (No way!)
番外の生放送
Was an extra live broadcast
すごく楽しくって (ええー！)
It was so much fun (Whoa!)
寝付けなかったんだ (にゃー！)
I couldn't fall asleep (Meow!)
特別なすごいことなんて
Things that are special and amazing
そう起こらない日常
Don't happen so often in daily life
だけどそのエッセンス
But that essence
儚い夢に変えて
I'll turn into a fleeting dream
毎日がパラダイス
Every day is paradise
思い切り遊んで笑っちゃう
I'll play to my heart's content and laugh
青春実況！イエーイ！
Youth live broadcasting! Yay!
涙を流す覚悟してきたー！ (うそつーけー！)
I came prepared to shed tears! (Li-ar!)
負ける気がしないんだって！
I don't feel like losing!
残念ですがここで試合終了だよ！ (うっそー！)
Sorry, but the game ends here! (No way!)
まだ終わりたくないー！
I don't want it to end yet!
どんな毎日も 楽しくなっちゃうんだ
Any day can become fun
だっていつだって
Because anytime,
ほら あなたが待ってるの (イエーイ！)
Look, you are waiting (Yay!)
みんなで毎日を (いっしょー！)
Everyone, every day (Together!)
出会えて嬉しい (新曲！)
I'm happy to have met you (New song!)
みんなと一緒なら (よいしょー！)
If I'm with everyone (Heave-ho!)
気分は最高潮
I'm in the best mood
窓の向こうの笑顔に手を振って
Waving my hand to the smiles beyond the window
配信中 届ける デイリーダイアリー
Delivering the Daily Diary through the stream
青春実況中 (いけーいけー)
Youth live broadcasting (Go, go!)
挑戦配信中 (ためしてみて)
Challenge streaming (Give it a try!)
青春実況中 (いっぱい)
Youth live broadcasting (Plenty!)
挑戦配信中 (あそぼおー)
Challenge streaming (Let's play!)
デイリーダイアリー
Daily Diary
届けよう
Let's deliver it
イエーイ！
Yay!
ということでね、2曲目はね...
So, for the second song...
夏色まつりが好きな曲で、わちゃわちゃしたいがためにね...
It's a song I like, and because I wanted to mess around...
みんなにお願いして歌いましたー！
I asked everyone to sing it with me!
イエーイ！楽しかったー！
Yay! That was fun!
いや、よかった。でもさ、なんか他のホロメンの曲というかさ...
Man, that was great. But you know, songs of other Holo-members...
メンバーの曲って歌うことないじゃん。
We usually don't get to sing other members' songs.
ないねー。確かにー。
We don't. That's true.
そう、こういう機会でね、ぜひね、レアリティの高い...
So, through this opportunity, I definitely wanted you to hear...
他のホロメンの歌うデイリーダイアリーなんかも聴いていただけたらなと思って...
This high-rarity version of Daily Diary sung by other members...
選曲しましたよ。
So I chose this song.
めちゃくちゃ楽しかったー！
It was so much fun!
ということで、ここからは、せっかくこのメンバーがいるんだから...
And so, since we have all these members here...
スクショタイムをして...
Let's do a screenshot time...
ぜひみんなにもね、ツイートしていただきたいなと思うわけですよ。
I'd like everyone to tweet them out.
ツイートタイムー！
Tweet time!
じゃあまずね、ぎゅっと集まっていただいて...
Well first, please gather close together...
はあとちゃんはちょっとあれかな、隅にしてもらおう。
Haato-chan, maybe you should be over in the corner.
えー！？
What!?
ちゃまも、ちゃまも。でもぎゅっとなってね。
Chama too, Chama too. But stay close.
まず全員集合の、ぎゅっと！
First, everyone together, squeeze in!
ぎゅー！あやあや。
Squeeze! Aya-aya.
こうかな。どうですか？
Like this? How's it look?
ぎゅーってなってますね。
We're all squeezed together.
可愛く撮ってくださいねー。はい、チーズ！
Please take a cute picture. Okay, cheese!
あ、いい、それ！キュンだ！
Oh, that's nice! Kyun!
きゅんです！
Kyun-desu!
ちょっとまつり、一人ずつやりたいのがあるんですけど。
Matsuri, there's something I want to do with each of you one by one.
ハートをこうやってまつりと作ってくれる人募集中でーす！
I'm looking for people to make a heart with me like this!
よし。よし、じゃあみんなで作るか。ハート。
Alright. Alright, then let's all make one. A heart.
誰か、誰か作って。じゃあ、まつちゃんと。
Someone, someone make it with me. Then, with Matsu-chan.
まず、まっちゃんと... ちょっと待って。
First, with Matsu-chan... Wait a second.
はい。ハート！
Okay. Heart!
ハート！
Heart!
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
ありがとう！嬉しい！
Thank you! I'm so happy!
嬉しい、嬉しい。最高のプレゼントだぜ。
I'm so happy, so happy. This is the best present ever.
じゃあ続いて、ちょっと来てください。
Next, please come over here.
メルメルやるね。
I'll do Mel-Mel next.
はい。ハート。なってる？
Okay. Heart. Is it working?
おお！
Oh!
なってるかな？ちょっと...
I wonder if it is? Wait...
頑張れ、メル！頑張れ！
Hang in there, Mel! Hang in there!
オッケー、オッケー。真の力を！なってる、なってる、なってる！
Okay, okay. Show your true power! It's working, it's working!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
おめでとう、まつりちゃん！
Congratulations, Matsuri-chan!
ありがとうございます。じゃあ最後に嫁。
Thank you very much. Lastly, my wife.
嫁おいで。
Come here, wife.
嫁、あ、はい。嫁って呼ばれるの...？
Wife, oh, yes. Who's being called wife...?
ほら、ほら！オタクのチェキ撮ろうぜ。
Come on, come on! Let's do a 'Cheki' of an otaku.
ちょっと、オタクの...
Wait, an otaku's...
こうやろうとしたら「ぐぅ」みたいに...
I was trying to do this, but then it went 'guu'...
よっしゃ！それ、オタクのチェキ。
Alright! That's an otaku's Cheki.
あれ？おかしいな。オタクのチェキ...
Wait? That's weird. An otaku's Cheki...
おかしいな。私、誕生日なんですけど。
That's weird. I'm the one whose birthday it is!
誕生日だぞ、こっちは！
It's my birthday, you know!
あ！やった！やったー！
Ah! We did it! We did it!
これレアですね！レア、レア。
This is rare! Rare, rare.
ありがとう！いえーい！
Thank you! Yay!
嬉しい、嬉しい。嬉しいでございますよ。
I'm so happy, so happy. I am truly happy.
もう大丈夫か？他にない？他に何かやり残したことは？
Are we okay now? Anything else? Is there anything else you want to do?
ガチ恋距離でさ、なんかみんな映れないかな？
Can we all get in the shot from a really close distance?
みんなアップで映れるかな？集合！
Can we all get close-ups? Everyone, gather round!
集合！耳だけでもいい、自分。
Gather round! Just my ear is fine for me.
なんで、なんで？！
Why, why?!
ああー！
Ahhh!
もっと、もっと近づいてほしい。もっと？
I want you to get even closer. More?
あ、にょき！にょき！いいね、近い！
Ah, peek! Peek! Nice, it's close!
しゃがまなくてもいいんだ。これ。はい。
You don't even have to crouch. Like this. Okay.
いえーい！いえーい！いえーい！
Yay! Yay! Yay!
いいねー。こういうのが撮りたかった。いや、よいですな。
Nice. This is the kind of shot I wanted to take. It's really good.
ちょっと、はあとちゃんさ、真ん中入って。
Wait, Haato-chan, go in the middle.
はあとちゃん、まつりちゃん真ん中じゃなくていいの？
Haato-chan, is it okay if Matsuri-chan isn't in the middle?
いいよ、いいよ。邪魔！
It's fine, it's fine. Out of the way!
じゃあ、はあとちゃんがこの辺で。で、メルメル頑張って。
Then Haato-chan around here. And Mel-Mel, hang in there.
メル、メルメル、ちょっと前、前。前行って。はあちゃん、前来て。
Mel, Mel-Mel, come a bit more to the front. To the front. Ha-chan, come to the front.
はい、はい、はい。これで... ちらっ！ちらっ！
Okay, okay, okay. With this... Peek! Peek!
ちら！いえーい！いえーい！いえーい！
Peek! Yay! Yay! Yay!
いえーい！いえーい！いえーい！いえーい！
Yay! Yay! Yay! Yay!
オッケー、オッケー。撮れてる、撮れてる！撮れてる！いえーい！
Okay, okay. We're taking it! We're taking it! Yay!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
いえーい！ということで、なかなかいいんじゃないですかね？
Yay! So, isn't this pretty good?
よいですな。よいですね、よいですね。
It's good. It's good, it's good.
いや、満足しました。満足しました！はい。
Man, I'm satisfied. I'm satisfied! Yes.
ということで、じゃあね。ちょっとまだまだ続いての曲もありますので。
So then, well. We still have more songs coming up.
お楽しみに！ちょっとここから一人になるの不安だなぁ。
Please look forward to them! I'm a bit worried about being alone from here on.
ああー。不安だから円陣でも組んでさ。みんなの力がほしいなぁ。
Ah... I'm worried, so let's do a huddle. I want everyone's strength.
しょうがないなぁ。やっちゃおう、やっちゃおうぜ！
Can't be helped then. Let's do it, let's do it!
じゃあちょっと円陣。はい。
Okay, let's huddle. Okay.
ひよってんのか、まつり！
Are you scared, Matsuri?!
ひよってる！はあとちゃん、おいで！ちゃまちゃん、ちゃまちゃんもおいで！
I'm scared! Haato-chan, come here! Chama-chan, you come here too!
ちゃまちゃんもおいで。それじゃあ...
Chama-chan, come here too. Okay then...
掛け声を。掛け声どうしよう。どんなのがいいかな？
Let's do a chant. What kind of chant should we do?
まつり総長！まつり総長！
Matsuri President! Matsuri President!
何か、何か一言！はあとちゃん、反対だね。はあと！はあと！おいで！
Give us a word! Haato-chan, you're on the wrong side! Haato! Haato! Come here!
反対じゃない。反対じゃなかった。あ、ちょ...
You're on the wrong side. No, you weren't. Ah, wait...
あれ？ちょ、はあとちゃんも消えた！真っ白だけど！
Wait? Ah, Haato-chan disappeared too! She's all white!
ちゃま真っ白になっちゃった！嘘だろ。
Chama became all white! No way.
それじゃ、何？はい。じゃあ。
So then, what? Okay. Then.
まつりこの後も頑張るし。来年のね。
Matsuri will keep doing her best after this... and next year's...
あの、6月1日か2日かちょっとわかんないですけど。
...June 1st or 2nd, I don't know which yet, but...
またみんなで集まって。4周年、そして5周年も...
...let's all gather again. For the 4th anniversary, and then the 5th anniversary too...
頑張って楽しく活動を続けていきましょう！
...I'll do my best and continue my activities while having fun!
じゃあ、まつりが「まつりのこと...」って言ったら、みんなが「愛してるぞー！」って言って。
So, when Matsuri says "About Matsuri...", everyone say "We love you!"
こうしよう。わかった。じゃあ、いくよ！はい。
Let's do that. Got it. Here we go! Okay.
まつりのこと...！
About Matsuri...!
愛してるぞー！いえーい！
We love you! Yay!
ありがとうございます。頑張ってね、まつりちゃん！
Thank you very much. Do your best, Matsuri-chan!
頑張れる、頑張れる。ありがとう！
I can do it, I can do it. Thank you!
それじゃあ、またお会いしましょう。はい。
Well then, see you again. Bye.
またね！見てるぞ！見てるぞ！ありがとうございます。頑張ってね。
Bye-bye! We're watching! We're watching! Thank you. Do your best.
またね！セッシャ！セッシャ！セッシャ！
See you! Sessha! Sessha! Sessha!
セッシャ！セッシャ！いや、よかった。もう本当にありがとう。
Sessha! Sessha! Man, that was great. Truly, thank you.
あれ？なんか今「セッシャ」って言った気がしたけど。いや、よかった。
Wait? I felt like I just heard a "Sessha" just now. Man, it was great.
なんか、やっぱりあのメンバーが一番安心しますね。あれ？はあとちゃん？
I really feel most at ease with that group of members. Wait? Haato-chan?
はあとちゃんは残りたいてい... あれ、消えた。
Haato-chan said she wanted to stay... oh, she disappeared.
ということでね。どんどん続いての曲に参りましょう！
So then. Let's move on to the next song!
もっと もっと 上がるよ空に
Higher and higher, they'll rise into the sky
大きな夏の花
Big summer flowers
君と眺める夏の花
The Summer Flower I Gaze at with You
ふらふら歩くよ楽しい 香りに誘われて
I walk unsteadily, invited by the pleasant scent
カラコロ響く下駄の音
The clattering sound of clogs
どこまでも
Wherever it goes
キラキラ輝く屋台の
The glittering stalls
明りに飛び込んで
Leaping into the light
ピカピカ頬張る真っ赤な
Munching on a bright red
いちご飴
Strawberry candy
さあどんとぱっとね
Come on, with a boom and a flash
ずっと待ってた
I've been waiting forever
ほらね今年も花火が打ち上がる
Look, the fireworks are going up again this year
さあ祭りだ祭りだ祭りだワッショイ
Come on, it's a festival, a festival, a festival! Wasshoi!
いっちにのさんので声出して
One, two, three, let's shout
手と手を繋いで叫ぶよワッショイ
Hand in hand, we shout! Wasshoi!
まだまだ上がるよ
There's more to come
今夜の花火もテンションも
Tonight's fireworks and our excitement
ガヤガヤ賑やか見るもの
The noisy and lively surroundings
全てが眩しくて
Everything is so bright
シャクシャク溶けかけ頬張る
Munching on the melting
かき氷
Shaved ice
さあバンバカバカやって
Come on, let's go wild
クスクス笑わせて
Make everyone giggle
君の笑顔の花火が打ち上がる
The fireworks of your smile are going up
さあ楽しい祭りだ止まるなワッショイ
Come on, it's a fun festival, don't stop! Wasshoi!
弾けるリズムを最後まで
Keep the bursting rhythm going until the end
浴衣も忘れて跳ねるよワッショイ
Forgetting about the yukata, we leap! Wasshoi!
もっともっと上がるよ
Higher and higher
空に大きな夏の華
A big summer flower in the sky
わたあめ頬張り溶けるよ一瞬
Eating cotton candy, it melts in an instant
輝く時間も溶けてゆく
The shining moments are melting away too
君との想い出溶けない一生
The memories with you will never melt
消えない宝物
An eternal treasure
祭りだ祭りだ祭りだワッショイ
It's a festival, a festival, a festival! Wasshoi!
流れる光に照らされて
Illuminated by the flowing lights
全てが眩しい想い出ワッショイ
Everything is a dazzling memory! Wasshoi!
もっともっと輝け
Shine more and more
君と眺める夏の華
The summer flower I watch with you
はい。君と眺める夏の花でした。
Yes. That was "Summer Flower Watched with You".
ありがとうございました。
Thank you very much.
いや、久しぶりに、VROOM! ぶりにね、ちょっと踊ったんで、
Well, I danced for the first time in a while, since VROOM!,
合ってたかな？あ、ちょっと不安だなーって思いながら踊りました。
so I wondered if I got it right? I was dancing while thinking, "Ah, I'm a little anxious."
そして、ちょっとね、なんか変わったんですよ。
And, you know, something changed.
何が変わったかわかるかーい？
Do you know what changed?
そう、ここ！さっきまで出てなかったホログラムを出してみました。
That's right, here! I tried putting out a hologram that wasn't there until just now.
どう？おしゃれじゃない？
How is it? Isn't it stylish?
これもね、あの、この日のためにね、準備しました。
I prepared this for this day as well.
ちなみに、このしなぎもスピーカーとさっきのマイクとこのイヤホンマイク？
By the way, this Shinagimo speaker, the microphone from before, and this earphone mic?
全部ね、あの、まつりのパパである、皆村パパが
All of them were designed by Matsuri's father,
デザインをしてくれたんですよ。ありがとうございます！
Minamura-papa. Thank you very much!
それでは、えー、ちょっとここで告知タイムを挟みたいと、
Now, uh, I'd like to insert an announcement time here,
挟みたいというかまあそろそろ時間なんですけど、告知タイムをしたいと思います！
or rather, it's about time, so I'll do an announcement time!
それでは、1つ目はもうみんな知ってると思うんですけど、
Well, I think everyone already knows the first one, but
こちら！どどん！
here it is! Ta-da!
7月22日22時より、えー、夏色まつりさん、
Starting from July 22nd at 22:00, uh, Natsuiro Matsuri-san—
さんって書いてある、ヤングドーナツセット発売決定です！
it says "san"—Young Donut set is confirmed for release!
なんと数量限定8,888！パチパチパチパチ！セット。
It's limited to 8,888 units! *Clap clap clap clap!* set.
限定なので、えー、この後22時からね、急いで買ってくださいね。
It's limited, so please hurry and buy it from 22:00 later, okay?
これ前回はちなみに、あの、5,000個だったんですけど、5分で売り切れましたので。
By the way, last time there were 5,000 units, and they sold out in 5 minutes.
あの、まあでも今回8,888個あるから、
But this time there are 8,888,
まあ前回よりはゆっくり買えるんじゃないかなーって思いますのでぜひぜひ手に入れてください。
so I think you'll be able to buy them more leisurely than last time, so please get your hands on them.
お願いします。キーホルダーとかも付きます。
Please. It also comes with things like keychains.
まつりが、あの、こういうポーズにしたいっていうデザインも考えたので、
Matsuri also thought of a design for the pose she wanted,
ぜひあの買ってください、手に入れてください。
so please buy it, please get it.
はい、そしてそして、続いて。えーなんとね、あの、よくあるやつですけども。
Yes, and then, moving on. Uh, it's one of those common things.
あ、やべ、後ろ向いて話してたのバレちゃった。ごめん。
Oh crap, I got caught talking while facing backwards. Sorry.
歩きながら喋ってもバレないやと思って...
I thought I wouldn't be caught if I spoke while walking...
こうやって喋ってたのバレちゃった。
I was caught speaking like this.
恥ずかしい。
Embarrassing.
あの... じゃあ、よく見える、こちらです！
Um... well, here's a better look!
ドーン！
Tada!
夏色まつり 誕生記念2021
7月22日 販売開始
Natsuiro Matsuri Birthday Commemoration 2021
Sales start July 22nd
え、夏色まつり誕生日記念2021ということで、
Since it's Natsuiro Matsuri's Birthday Commemoration 2021,
え、誕生日を記念した抱き枕カバーとSNS風アクリルキーホルダーを販売したいと思います！
I'll be selling a dakimakura cover and an SNS-style acrylic keychain to commemorate my birthday!
イェーイ！
Yay!
で、全体はこちら！
And here's the full lineup!
ドン！
Tada!
全体を見せたい。
I want to show the whole thing.
あ、これですね。これ。
Ah, this is it. This one.
えーっと、抱き枕カバーが表と裏があります。
Um, the dakimakura cover has front and back sides.
後で大きいの見せます。
I'll show a larger view later.
そして、あ、大きいの出た。これね。
And next, ah, a large one appeared. This one.
イラストはセラミク先生。
The illustration is by Ceramic-sensei.
あの、よく、あ、こよねの『歌ってみた』とか、おかゆの『歌ってみた』、
She often draws for Korone's "tried singing", Okayu's "tried singing",
まつりの『歌ってみた』も描いてるんですけど、
and Matsuri's "tried singing" as well.
いつもお世話になっております。
I'm always in her debt.
すごく可愛いデザインになっております。
It's a very cute design.
表はなんだか誘う感じになっていて、
The front has a somewhat inviting feel,
裏これ見えるかな？
Can you see the back?
ちょっと涙ぐんで『ふえー』ってなってるところなので、
She's a bit teary-eyed and going "fuee"...
是非手に入れてください。はい。
so please do get your hands on it. Yes.
そしてそして、アクリルキーホルダーがこちら。
And next, here's the acrylic keychain.
ですね。これは、『しー』みたいな感じになっております。
This has a "shh" kind of feeling.
これね、イルカなの。ここの上の部分、可愛いでしょ？
This is a dolphin. This top part, cute right?
あのね、魚の予定だったんだけど、ちょっと魚人気すぎたからイルカになりました。
It was planned to be a fish, but fish were a bit too popular, so it became a dolphin.
お魚、イルカ、まあ誤差ですね。
Fish, dolphin, well, it's a margin of error.
これを持ってね、お出かけすると、
If you take this with you when you go out,
あの、パシャって、こう、スマホかざしてアクリルキーホルダーをパシャって撮るとですね、
and hold up your smartphone and take a picture of the acrylic keychain,
あの、背景が透けてデートしてる風になるんですよ。
the background shows through and it looks like we're on a date.
で、ハッシュタグがあるんですけど、
And there's a hashtag,
『夏色デート』っていうハッシュタグが書いてあると思うんで、
I think the hashtag "Natsuiro Date" is written there,
これを付けてツイートするとなんと、
so if you tweet with this, surprisingly,
まつりから『今日のデート楽しかったね』ってリプライが来ます！
you'll get a reply from Matsuri saying "Today's date was fun"!
はい、送ります。
Yes, I'll send it.
あの、アカウント鍵とかで見れない限りは送りたいと思いますので、
As long as it's not a locked account, I want to send it,
是非購入してツイートしちゃってください。はい。
so please buy it and tweet it. Yes.
そしてね、特典でボイスも付きますので、
And also, voices are included as a bonus,
是非ね、ボイスも聞いてほしい。
so I really want you to listen to the voices too.
アクリルキーホルダーにぴったりなボイスと誕生日のなんかいい感じのボイスが付きます。
There's a voice perfect for the keychain and a nice birthday-themed voice.
はい。以上！
Yes. That's all!
ということでね、そんな感じのグッズは22日の20時かな？くらいから販売いたしますので、
So, those goods will be on sale from around 20:00 on the 22nd,
よろしくお願いします。
so please look forward to it.
ということでそろそろもう50分になってね、時間が迫ってきているのですが、
And it's already almost 50 minutes past, time is running out,
今日は楽しんでくれたかな？くれたかな？
but did you enjoy yourselves today? Did you?
この後22時30分より、プレミア公開で、あの動画が公開されるんですよ。
After this, from 22:30, that video will be released as a premiere.
何の動画かな？何の動画かな？楽しみだよね。
What video could it be? What video could it be? Exciting, isn't it?
その動画とは... ふんっ。
That video is... Hmph.
ということで、ライブはちょっと残念なんですけど、ここで終わり...
So, it's a bit sad for the live, but it ends here...
ではなく！最後の最後に、歌うか。
NOT! At the very last, shall I sing?
ちょっと、よいしょ。
Just a bit, heave-ho.
出でよマイク。あ、来た。
Come forth, mic! Ah, it came.
最後の最後に聴いてほしい曲があります。
There's a song I want you to hear at the very end.
22時半からは、今から歌う曲のショートバージョンが上がるから、絶対見てくれよな。
At 22:30, the short version of the song I'm about to sing will be uploaded, so be sure to watch it.
ということで、最後までついてこいよ、まつりす！
So, follow me until the end, Matsurisu!
誕生日は最後まで終わらないぞ！
My birthday doesn't end until the very end!
それでは聴いてください。
Now, please listen.
『HiHiハイテンション！』
"HiHi High Tension!"
パッと満開 笑顔咲かせ
Bloom brightly, let smiles blossom
歌えよ踊れ
Sing and dance
実況 降臨 ショウタイム
Gameplay, descent, showtime
とびきりな祭り 始めよう
Let's start the most special festival
Y 真っ白ページ
Y, a pure white page
今 個性が集結
Now, individualities gather
Butterfly 次元も超えて
Butterfly, even crossing dimensions
君と思い出 重ねたら
When I layer memories with you
新しい未来へ
Towards a new future
嗚呼 見えなくたって
Ah, even if I can't see it
何故だろう伝わる
For some reason, it's conveyed
色とりどりの夢
Multi-colored dreams
花火みたい 打ち上がる
Rising up like fireworks
幕開けだ
The curtain rises
行こうよ ハイテンションもっと
Let's go, even more high tension!
ハイ ハイ ハイ 放って
High high high, let it out!
音に合わせて
Moving to the beat
私もここなら 主人公
I'm the protagonist here too
だから シャキッと 胸張って
So stand tall and proud
さあ ハイテンションいいね
Now, high tension is good, right?
ハイ ハイ ハイ 最高
High high high, the best!
笑顔見てたい だから
I want to see your smiles, so...
この瞬間が SHOWTIME!
This moment is SHOWTIME!
出会えた奇跡に スマイル
A smile for the miracle of meeting you
みんなで彩る ヒストリー
A history we all color together
ねえ 大きな声で
Hey, with a loud voice
お互いのエール 響いたら
When our cheers resonate together
ねえ つながる絆
Hey, the bonds that connect us
光り結び 生まれるんだ
Are born from the tying of light
私たちの世界
Our world
ちゃんと聞こえてるよ
I can hear you clearly
賑やかな未来が
A lively future
こんなにもときめくの
Makes my heart flutter this much
君の声 その瞳 キラキラ
Your voice, those eyes, sparkling
友情をさあ 巻き起こすぞ フェスティバル
Let's stir up a festival of friendship!
ハイテンションよっしゃー
High tension, alright!
ハイ ハイ ハイ 跳ねて
High high high, jump!
心合わせて
Our hearts as one
誰かが欠けても 駄目だよ
It's no good if anyone is missing
ハッピー エンジョイ ニコニコで ピース
Happy, enjoy, peace with a smile
ハイテンション歌え
High tension, sing!
ハイ ハイ ハイ 踊れ
High high high, dance!
笑顔こそ最強のパワー
A smile is the ultimate power
地球ごと レッツショータイム
The whole Earth, let's showtime!
とびきりのお祭りいいでしょ
This is an extraordinary festival, right?
まだまだこれから 行くよね
We're just getting started, right?
わっしょい わっしょい みんなで
Wasshoi, wasshoi, everyone!
わっしょい わっしょい 一緒に
Wasshoi, wasshoi, together!
わっしょい わっしょい わっしょい イェーイ
Wasshoi, wasshoi, wasshoi, yeah!
毎日が新発見
Every day is a new discovery
ぜんぶ楽しみ尽くして
Enjoy it all to the fullest
ひとつになってさ
Become as one
ハイ ハイ ジャンプ！
High high jump!
行くよ ハイテンションもっと
Here we go, even more high tension!
ハイ ハイ ハイ 放って
High high high, let it out!
音に合わせて
Moving to the beat
私もここなら 主人公
I'm the protagonist here too
だから シャキッと 胸張って
So stand tall and proud
さあ ハイテンションいいね
Now, high tension is good, right?
ハイ ハイ ハイ 最高
High high high, the best!
笑顔見てたい だから
I want to see your smiles, so...
この瞬間が SHOWTIME!
This moment is SHOWTIME!
出会えた奇跡に スマイル
A smile for the miracle of meeting you
みんなで彩る ヒストリー
A history we all color together
まつりが連れて行くよ
Matsuri will take you along
ほら 手を繋ごう
Come on, let's hold hands